

NAUSHIKHA JAYAWICKRAMA

Phone: +94 76331 6991

E-mail: hello@naushikha.com

Website: naushikha.com

COMPUTER ENTHUSIAST

PROFIL F

Hardworking, self-motivated ambitious programmer with a keen eye for detail. Excellent track record of performance in all tasks undertaken with nearly 3 years of cumulative industrial working experience in fields such as game testing, networking, customer support and tutoring.

Aiming to work in a challenging but friendly environment with a goal to become a part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

PLAYTESTER

Arimac (Jan 2021 - May 2021)

• Testing and evaluating Android mobile games

VIRTUAL INTERN

Nestlé (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

Researching for the supply-chain division to localize use of raw materials

SYSTEM ENGINEER

Telasis Solutions (2017 - 2019)

- System and network installation and administration
- Server and desktop hardware configuration

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

Voigue (Dec 2017 - Jan 2018)

 Support team services to handle Daraz.lk's excess user traffic during Christmas

INTERN

Third Space Global (Dec 2016 - Jan 2017)

• Online tutoring mathematics for school children stationed in the UK

SKILLS

- Linux, networking and system administration
- WebGL graphics and web design
- Hardware installation, upgrading and maintennance
- Quick learning
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Fluent communication

EDUCATION

BSC (HONS) COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Colombo School of Computing (2019 >>)

• Current GPA: 3.8

0/L, A/L

Ananda College, Colombo 10. (2003 - 2016)

• Ordinary Level : 9 As

• Advanced Level: Z-Score - 2.3634, Island Rank - 8, District Rank - 2





